A Guide to the Office of the Vice President for Administration, University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1976-1982
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Vice President for Administration, University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1976-1982
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/1/2.892
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1989 November 15.
Contents List
- Academic Calendar Committee 1976-1977 (Box 1)
- Academic Space 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- Academic Space-Administrator 1976-1977 (Box 1)
- Academic Space-Altschul 1978-1979 (Box 1)
- Academic Space-Tolbert 1978-1980 (Box 1)
- Academic Space-Asbestos Hazards 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- Academic Space-Assessments 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- Academic Space and Energy Management (2 folders) 1977-1978 (Box 2)
- Academic Space and Energy Management-Altschul 1979-1980 (Box 2)
- Academic Space Management (2 folders) 1981-1982 (Box 2)
- Administrative Building Committee 1981-1982 (Box 2)
- Alderman Library Security and Fire Protection System Committee 1981-1982 (Box 2)
- Annual Reports (2 folders) 1977-1982 (Box 2)
- Appalachian Power Company-see Virginia Electric Power Company (VEPCO) 1980-1981 (Box 2)
- Arboretum Committee 1976-1982 (Box 2)
- Auxiliary and Business Services 1976-1978 (Box 2)
- Bayly Museum Smoke and Heat Detection Committee 1980-1981 (Box 3)
- Birdwood 1979-1980 (Box 3)
- Birdwood-ad hoc Committee 1981-1982 (Box 3)
- Birdwood-Designer House 1979-1980 (Box 3)
- Birdwood-Farm 1976-1977 (Box 3)
- Birdwood-Golf Course 1981-1982 (Box 3)
- Blue Ridge-General 1978-1979 (Box 3)
- Blue Ridge-Planning Teams 1981-1982 (Box 3)
- Blue Ridge-Renovation Committee 1981-1982 (Box 3)
- Budgets (2 folders) 1976-1980 (Box 3)
- Budgets-Academic Space 1980-1982 (Box 4)
- Budgets-Amendments 1978-1979 (Box 4)
- Budgets-Blandy Farm 1980-1981 (Box 4)
- Budgets-Highway Research Council 1980-1982 (Box 4)
- Budgets-JAG School 1980-1982 (Box 4)
- Budgets-NRAO 1980-1982 (Box 4)
- Budgets-Risk Management 1980-1982 (Box 4)
- Budget Exhibit-U.Va. (2 folders) 1976-1977 (Box 4)
- Budget Office 1977-1982 (Box 4)
- Budget Office-Special Project Expenditures 1977-1978 (Box 4)
- Buildings and Grounds-General (6 folders) 1976-1981 (Box 5)
- Buildings and Grounds-Reports (6 folders) 1976-1981 (Box 6)
- Buildings and Grounds-Special Projects 1976-1987 (Box 7)
- Buildings and Grounds-Weekly Report Sheets 1977-1978 (Box 7)
- Buildings and Grounds-Work Requests 1976-1978 (Box 7)
- Business Operations 1978-1982 (Box 7)
- Capital Outlay (2 folders) 1977-1982 (Box 7)
- Capital Outlay Requests 1978-1979 (Box 8)
- Capital Outlay-Clinch Valley College 1978-1979 (Box 8)
- Capital Outlay-U.Va. 1978-1979 (Box 8)
- Capital Outlay-U.Va. Medical Center 1978-1979 (Box 8)
- Carruthers Hall Building Committee 1980-1981 (Box 8)
- Carter, Robert F. 1980-1981 (Box 8)
- Chamber of Commerce 1976-1978 (Box 8)
- Children's Rehab Center Addition Building Committee 1980-1981 (Box 8)
- Cleveland Transit System Buses 1976-1977 (Box 8)
- Clinical Chemistry Lab Building Committee 1980-1981 (Box 8)
- Colonnade Club 1976-1981 (Box 8)
- Comptroller's Office (2 folders) 1976-1982 (Box 9)
- Comptroller's Office-Assistant Comptroller's Office 1976-1977 (Box 9)
- Comptroller's Office-Courier Service 1976-1977 (Box 9)
- Computer Graphic Committee 1980-1981 (Box 9)
- Continuing Education-Norfolk 1977-1978 (Box 9)
- Cook, Brenda S. (Restricted) 1980-1981 (Box 9)
- Copeley/GSBA Phase II 1977-1978 (Box 9)
- Copeley Hill Phase V-Building Committee 1980-1981 (Box 9)
- Cost Proposal-U.Va. Medical Center 1977-1978 (Box 9)
- Creating an Accessible Campus 1978-1979 (Box 9)
- Education Lease 1977-1978 (Box 9)
- Energy Committee Student Survey 1976-1977 (Box 9)
- Energy Conservation Committee 1981-1982 (Box 9)
- Engineering Research Building Committee 1981-1982 (Box 9)
- Equal Opportunity 1976-1982 (Box 10)
- Evaluation of Sites-U.Va.Parking Garage 1978-1979 (Box 10)
- Executive Programs Center (3 folders) 1978-1981 (Box 10)
- Exxon Service Station 1977-1978 (Box 10)
- Facilities Engineering 1979-1981 (Box 10)
- "Fairhill"-Volm Property 1979-1980 (Box 10)
- Fan Mountain Lease-Ray Peterson 1979-1980 (Box 10)
- Fire Inspections (3 folders) 1976-1979 (Box 11)
- Garrett Hall Renovation Committee 1981-1982 (Box 11)
- Gas Contract 1979-1980 (Box 11)
- Gilmer Hall Addition-Building Committee 1980-1981 (Box 11)
- Goals 1979-1980 (Box 11)
- Goodrich Tire Contract 1979-1980 (Box 11)
- Guidelines for Use of Services 1980-1981 (Box 11)
- Gus Steak House 1977-1978 (Box 11)
- Halsey Hall 1976-1977 (Box 11)
- Handicap Access Committee 1979-1980 (Box 11)
- Handicapped Alterations 1978-1979 (Box 11)
- Handicapped Committee 1977-1978 (Box 11)
- Heating Plant-Fuel and Tonage 1976-1977 (Box 12)
- Heating Plant-General 1976-1980 (Box 12)
- Heating Plant-Reports 1977-1978 (Box 12)
- Housing Committee 1976-1977 (Box 12)
- Howard, John 1980-1981 (Box 12)
- Insurance-Marsh & McLennan, Inc. 1980-1981 (Box 12)
- Insurance Proposals-U.Va. (2 folders) 1979-1980 (Box 12)
- Invoices (2 folders) 1978-1981 (Box 13)
- JAG School 1976-1977 (Box 13)
- LaFon Apartments-Psychiatry 1976-1977 (Box 13)
- Lambeth/Copeley Housing-Phase IV 1980-1981 (Box 13)
- Lambeth Field Housing-Subcommittees 1976-1977 (Box 13)
- Law/GSBA Snack Bar 1977-1978 (Box 13)
- Lease Medical Center (2 folders) 1979-1980 (Box 13)
- Leases 1976-1982 (Box 13)
- Legal Adviser's Office 1977-1981 (Box 13)
- Legal Adviser's Office-Leases 1977-1982 (Box 13)
- Madison Hall Renovation Committee 1981-1982 (Box 14)
- Master Plan Committee (2 folders) 1981-1982 (Box 14)
- Master Plan Review Study-U.Va. Medical Center (2 folders) 1981-1982 (Box 14)
- Medical Center-Estimates 1977-1978 (Box 14)
- Medical Center-General (1 of 2) 1977-1982 (Box 14)
- Medical Center-General (2 of 2) 1977-1982 (Box 15)
- Medical Center-Levine Transmittals 1978-1979 (Box 15)
- Medical Center-Long Range Planning Committee 1977-1979 (Box 15)
- Medical Center-Master Plan Committee 1979-1981 (Box 15)
- Medical Center-Parking Garage 1978-1979 (Box 15)
- Medical Center-Planning 1976-1978 (Box 15)
- Medical Center-Planning and Construction Outline 1976-1977 (Box 15)
- Medical Center-Planning Outline 1980-1981 (Box 15)
- Medical Center-Reports 1976-1978 (Box 15)
- Medical Center-Space Analysis 1976-1977 (Box 15)
- Medlab Lease-Clinical Pathology 1979-1980 (Box 16)
- Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1976-1982 (Box 16)
- Motor Vehicle Safety Program 1976-1977 (Box 16)
- National Association of College and University Business Officers (NACUBO) (2 folders) 1976-1978 (Box 16)
- National Association of College and University Business Officers (NACUBO) (4 folders) 1978-1982 (Box 17)
- Newcomb Hall Committee 1978-1979 (Box 17)
- Office Supply Invoices 1977-1978 (Box 17)
- Parking and Transportation 1976-1989 (Box 17)
- Parking and Transportation-Mileage Reports 1980-1981 (Box 17)
- Pathology/Neuropathology Cancer Research Committee 1980-1981 (Box 18)
- Pavilion II-Hammond 1976-1977 (Box 18)
- Peabody/Newcomb Renovation and Addition 1980-1981 (Box 18)
- Personnel (2 folders) 1977-1982 (Box 18)
- Personnel-New Positions and Reallocations 1979-1980 (Box 18)
- Personnel-Search Committee for Vice President 1979-1980 (Box 18)
- Physical Planning Review Committee (1-3 of 4) 1980-1982 (Box 18)
- Physical Planning Review Committee (4 of 4) 1980-1982 (Box 19)
- Physical Planning Review-Special Projects 1979-1980 (Box 19)
- Physical Plant 1981-1982 (Box 19)
- Planning-Status Reports 1979-1980 (Box 19)
- Planning-State Council of Higher Education 1979-1980 (Box 19)
- Planning Department (3 folders) 1976-1979 (Box 19)
- Planning Department (2 folders) 1979-1982 (Box 20)
- Planning Department-B & E Code of Virginia 1978-1979 (Box 20)
- Planning Department-Renovation and Construction 1977-1978 (Box 20)
- Planning Department-Space Utilization Study 1977-1978 (Box 20)
- Planning Department-Standards Book 1980-1981 (Box 20)
- Planning for the Period-U.Va. 1977-1978 (Box 20)
- Planning Study-U.Va. Hospitals 1977-1978 (Box 20)
- Police 1976-1977 (Box 20)
- Police-Building Committee 1980-1981 (Box 20)
- Police-Department 1977-1980 (Box 20)
- President's Office 1976-1981 (Box 21)
- President's Office-Catlin 1976-1979 (Box 21)
- President's Office-Directives 1981-1982 (Box 21)
- President's Office-Executive Vice President (3 folders) 1976-1980 (Box 21)
- President's Office-Executive Vice President (2 folders) 1980-1982 (Box 22)
- President's Office-General 1977-1982 (Box 22)
- President's Office-JLARC 1977-1978 (Box 22)
- President's Office-Legislature 1978-1979 (Box 22)
- President's Office-Reports and Directives 1980-1981 (Box 22)
- President's Office-Visiting Team 1979-1980 (Box 22)
- Primary Care Center (2 folders) 1978-1979 (Box 22)
- Primary Care Center 1980-1981 (Box 23)
- Private Fund Requests 1977-1978 (Box 23)
- Projects-Booker House 1977-1978 (Box 23)
- Projects-Brooks Hall Renovation 1977-1978 (Box 23)
- Projects-Colonnade Walks 1977-1978 (Box 23)
- Projects-Lambeth Field Colonnades 1977-1978 (Box 23)
- Projects-Rotunda Forecourt 1977-1978 (Box 23)
- Real Property 1981-1982 (Box 23)
- Red Cross Building-Midmont Lane 1976-1977 (Box 23)
- Request for Proposal-U.Va. Medical Center 1977-1978 (Box 23)
- Research Division-Policy Council 1977-1981 (Box 23)
- Research Support 1976-1977 (Box 23)
- Risk Management (2 folders) 1979-1981 (Box 23)
- Risk Management 1981-1982 (Box 24)
- Risk Management-Bayly Museum Improvements 1981-1982 (Box 24)
- Risk Management-Charles Lunsford 1979-1980 (Box 24)
- Risk Management-Rogers & Company 1981-1982 (Box 24)
- Risk Management-Safety Coordinator 1979-1980 (Box 24)
- Risk Management-Safety Director 1980-1982 (Box 24)
- Risk Manger 1978-1979 (Box 24)
- Risk Manager Resumes 1978-1979 (Box 24)
- Rotunda 1976-1977 (Box 24)
- Safety Coordinator 1978-1979 (Box 25)
- Safety and Fire Protection Plan 1978-1979 (Box 25)
- Scott Stadium Renovation 1978-1979 (Box 25)
- Security and General Safety Committee 1977-1981 (Box 25)
- Mr. Shea-Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box 25)
- Southeastern Organ Procurement Foundation 1979-1980 (Box 25)
- Special Projects Committee (2 folders) 1976-1982 (Box 25)
- Sponsored Programs 1977-1978 (Box 25)
- Sprinkler/Smoke Detection System Building Committee 1980-1981 (Box 25)
- Statistical Information-U.Va. 1976-1977 (Box 26)
- Student Affairs (2 folders) 1976-1982 (Box 26)
- Student Council 1976-1977 (Box 26)
- Student Housing Building Committee 1980-1981 (Box 26)
- Student Recreation Building 1978-1979 (Box 26)
- Study of Projected SCHEV Guide-U.Va. 1979-1980 (Box 26)
- Task Force-University Neighborhood Study 1980-1981 (Box 26)
- Technical Evaluation of Rolm VLCBX 1979-1980 (Box 26)
- Telecommunications Committee 1977-1979 (Box 26)
- Telecommunications Management Corp. (2 folders) 1979-1980 (Box 27)
- Telephones 1979-1982 (Box 27)
- Telephones-Approved Outside 1976-1977 (Box 27)
- Telephones-Booz-Allen 1979-1980 (Box 27)
- Telephones-Committee 1978-1980 (Box 27)
- Telephones-Credit Cards 1978-1980 (Box 27)
- Telephones-General 1977-1979 (Box 27)
- Telephones-Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box 27)
- Telephones-Requests (1 of 2) 1976-1977 (Box 27)
- Telephones-Requests (2 of 2) 1976-1977 (Box 28)
- Telephones-SCATS 1976-1978 (Box 28)
- Thornton Hall Electrical System Building Committee 1980-1981 (Box 28)
- Traffic Control Committee 1976-1977 (Box 28)
- Treasurer's Office 1976-1982 (Box 28)
- Trouble Shooters Meeting 1976-1978 (Box 28)
- Undergraduate Readers Library (2 folders) 1978-1981 (Box 28)
- University Hall-Phase III 1980-1981 (Box 29)
- University Telephone Committee 1976-1978 (Box 29)
- University Union 1976-1977 (Box 29)
- University Union-Pavilion XI 1976-1977 (Box 29)
- Utilities Committee 1976-1980 (Box 29)
- Vehicle 1976-1977 (Box 29)
- Virginia Electric Power Company (VEPCO)-Appalachian Power Company (2 folders) 1980-1981 (Box 29)
- Virginia Electric Power Company (VEPCO)-Governor's Negotiating Committee 1976-1978 (Box 30)
- Virginia Electric Power Company (VEPCO)-Governor's Negotiating Team (2 folders) 1981-1982 (Box 30)
- Virginia's Geenral Assembly-Joint Legislative Audit and Review 1976-1977 (Box 30)
- Water Conservation Committee 1978-1981 (Box 30)
- Water Distribution and Fire Protection Committees 1980-1981 (Box 30)